export const foodieFunFacts = [
	{
		question: 'Which fruit resembles 60% of human DNA?',
		options: ['Strawberry', 'Bananas', 'Apples', 'Orange'],
		correctOption: 1,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which country did the french fries originate from?',
		options: ['France', 'USA', 'UK', 'Belgium'],
		correctOption: 3,
		points: 15,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which food never rots and doesn’t require preservatives to keep fresh?',
		options: ['Tea', 'Honey', 'Peanuts', 'Oats'],
		correctOption: 1,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which food contains the most calories per gram?',
		options: ['Chocolate', 'Chia seeds', 'Avocado', 'Pistachio'],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Among the numerous pizza toppings, which is the most commonly used?',
		options: ['Extra cheese', 'Mushrooms', 'Pepperoni', 'Pineapple'],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 15,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Which was the first country to set the minimum drinking age to 21?',
		options: ['Netherlands', 'Scotland', 'Germany', 'England'],
		correctOption: 3,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question: 'Which traditional Goan sweet can have up to 16 layers?',
		options: ['Cocada', 'Bebinca', 'Dodol', 'Serradura'],
		correctOption: 1,
		points: 15,
	},
	{
		question:
			"What is the staple food of almost one-third of the world's population?",
		options: ['Wheat', 'Bread', 'Rice', 'Lentils'],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 10,
	},
	{
		question: '‍How many pairs of chopsticks does China consume in a year?',
		options: ['20 billion', '1 billion', '45 billion', '100 million'],
		correctOption: 2,
		points: 15,
	},
	{
		question:
			'In which country would you find shish kebab as an everyday food?',
		options: ['Palau', 'India', 'Chile', 'Turkey'],
		correctOption: 3,
		points: 10,
	},
];
